Bernard L. Fontana Papers 1832-2000 (bulk 1956-1985)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series III: Correspondence
  - RAW – ROL., 1996-1999 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Rea, Amadeo Michael., 1975-1991 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - REJ – RI., 1970-1992 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - RIG – RZ., 1956-1962 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - RJ – RON., 1972-1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - ROM – SAY., 1990-1995 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - ROM – SHI., 1993-1997 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - ROM – SHI., 1998 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - ROM – SHI., 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - ROO – RZ., 1971-1992 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - S., 1967-1970 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - S- SAND, 1955-1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - S- SCG., 1963-1966 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - S – SH., 1956-1962 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - SANE – SAX., 1963-1992 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - SAY – SCHE., 1967-1990 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Sayers, Robert., 1971-1990 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - SAZ – SHI., 1990-1995 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - SCH – SCN., 1963-1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - SCHF – SCHUL., 1971-1990 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - SCHUM – SD., 1971-1990 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Schuster, Carl., 1963-1969 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - SCO – SK., 1963-1966 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - SE – SHEL., 1971-1989 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - SHEM – SHER., 1973-1991 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - SHJ – SOZ., 1992-1995 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - SHJ – THO (1 of 2)., 1995-1997 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - SHJ – THO (2 of 2)., 1995-1997 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - SHJ – THO., 1997-1997 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - SHJ – THO., 1998-1999 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Shutler, Richard., 1960-1967 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - SI – SN., 1956-1962 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Simmons, Marc., 1973-1992 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Simmons, Norman., 1962-1969 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - SJ – SN., 1974-1990 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - SL – SS., 1963-1966 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Watson., 1974-1983 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Wilson., 1984-1989 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - SOT – SOU., 1956-1962 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - SOB – SOR., 1973-1990 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - SOT – SOU., 1975-1992 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - SOV – STAO., 1971-1991 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - SPA – THO., 1990-1995 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - ST – SZ., 1963-1966 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - STAP – STI., 1971-1991 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - STJ – SZ., 1971-1992 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Sturtevant, William C., 1963-1970 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Sturtevant, William C., 1971-1982 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Swadesh, Frances., 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - T., 1963-1966 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - T – THI., 1971-1992 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - T – V., 1956-1962 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - T – V., 1967-1970 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Temple, David., 1959-1961 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - THJ – TON., 1973-1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - THO – WEB., 1995-1997 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - THO – WEB., 1997-1998 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - THO – WEB., 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Thompson, Raymond H., 1964-1970 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Thompson, Raymond H., 1970-1988 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - THP – WEB., 1990-1995 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - TOO – TOW., 1973-1992 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - TRA – TZ., 1972-1992 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - U., 1974-1991 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - U – V., 1961-1966 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - VAL – VAS., 1973-1991 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - VED – VEN., 1972-1986 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - VER – VZ., 1971-1991 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - W – WATS., 1971-1991 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - W – WH., 1967-1970 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - W – Z., 1956-1962 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - W – Z., 1963-1966 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - W – Z., 1967-1970 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Ward, Albert., 1975-1987 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Warren, David., 1971-1989 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - WATT – WEN., 1971-1990 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - WEC – Z., 1990-1995 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - WEC – Z., 1995-1997 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - WEC – Z., 1997-1998 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - WEC – Z., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - WED – WG., 1977-1991 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - WH – WIE., 1962-1992 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Wheeler, Joe L., 1972-1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - WIF – WN., 1979-1984 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Williford, Grace (Smith)., 1920-1959 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, Jack., 1976-1988 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Wilson, Maggie., 1971-1987 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - WO – WZ., 1960-1991 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Wroth, Will., 1980-1992 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Wyman, Leland., 1970-1989 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Y – Z., 1967-1991 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Zwinger, Ann., 1984-1992 (Box 39, Folder 16)
- Series IV: Personal Files
  Arrangement: Alphabetical. This series contains documents such as employment information, logs, awards and other personal materials.
  - Applications., 1956-1970 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Annual Reviews., 1983-1991 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Awards and Certificates., undated; 1956-1991 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Book Orders., 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Books of the Southwest Log., 1988-1989 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Curriculum Vitae and Resume., 1974-1992 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Disposed Books., 1987 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Letter Log., 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Phone Log., 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Powell, Lawrence Clark (90th Birthday)., 1996 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Sabbatical Leave., 1986 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Scuba Diving., undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - University of Arizona Employment., 1968-1992 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Visitor Log., 1988-1989 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Series V: Oversize
  Arrangement: Alphabetical. This series contains oversize materials.
  - Awards and Certificates., undated (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Illustrations., undated (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Maps and Posters., undated; 1952-1991 (Box 41, Folder 3)